Geofrey Isiagi

Phone: +256777963365
Address: Kampala, Uganda
Email: isiagigeofrey0@gmail.com

YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@isiagi_dev9769 **LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/isiagi-geofrey-ba91b1128/

Professional Summary

Multitalented software developer with experience in the Web software industry. Demonstrated excellent skills in HTML, JavaScript, CSS3, ReactJS, NodeJS, NextJs,

TypeScript, Github, and learning Python, Mobile Development in React Native with Udemy, and Cloud Development with

Udacity.

I have also engaged in some basic Data Science and Machine Learning studies.

I am a True team player with strengths in adaptability and accuracy.

Work Experience

04/2022 - 08/2022

HappiTech, Kampala

Software Developer, Frontend Reactjs,

- Developed in-house web solutions.
- Debugged and Maintained CodeBase
- Gathered and defined customer requirements to develop clear specifications for project plans.

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Outbox Uganda, Kampala

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (Full stack) / MENTOR,

- I was among the team developing an in-house enrollment application.
- Acted as a Mentor to the student developer.

May 2021 - Jul 2021

AirDady, Hoima

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, Frontend Reactis, Backend Nodejs,

- Engaged in the development of the Airdady API.
- Integrated the Api with a Reactjs Client.
- Debugged and Maintained CodeBase

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

Outbox Uganda, Kampala

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ INTERN, Frontend Reactjs, Backend Django,

- Collaborated in UNFPA project called GETIN
- Used Reactis for Frontend and Diango backend
- Debugged and Maintained CodeBase
- Gathered and defined customer requirements to develop clear specifications for project plans.
- Revised, modularized, and updated old code bases to modern development standards, reducing operating costs and improving functionality.
- Had an introduction and work with cloud technologies.

Jul 2020 - Sep 2020

Outbox Uganda, Kampala

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/ LEARNING FACILITATOR,

- Trained, and managed a team of developers, and discussed issues in order to provide resolution and apply best practices.
- Translated verbal customer requirements into written use cases and testable development stories.
- Acted as a Product Owner.
- Acted as a Product Manager

Outbox Uganda, Kampala

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/TRAINEE,

- Develop a Restaurant Menu Website as part of the Capstone Project in collaboration with one member at Outbox.
- Develop an Inventory Management API (NodeJS) in collaboration with 3 members of the team at Outbox.
- Engaged in coding BootCamp

Education

Aug 2016 - May 2021

Makerere University Business School

Bachelor of Business Statistics,

• Did data analysis with Epi data, excel, spss and stata.

Languages

English

— C2

Additional Skills

- Html
- Css3
- Javascript
- Reactis
- Nodejs
- MongoDB
- · Basic SQL
- Spss
- Stata
- Excel
- Epi Data
- Typescript
- Python
- · Basic Data Science and Machine Learning
- Cloud Development AWS
- React Native
- Interpersonal Skills

References

Available upon request